제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주, 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
1977년 1월 21일
January 21st, 1977
금요일 오후
Friday Afternoon
에릭네 차고 앞
Eric Forman's Driveway
야, 포먼
Forman, man.
그냥 쬐끔 긁힌 거잖아
아저씬 못 알아 보실 거야
It's a tiny, little scratch.
And Red's never gonna see it.
아니, 아빤 다 아셔
No, Red sees everything. He sees
when I put cheap gas in the car.
내가 싸구려 기름 넣으면
바로 알아내시는 걸
좋은 수가 있어
I got it.
이 위에다 내 "Gas, Grass, or Ass"
범퍼 스티커를 붙이는 거야
We'll put my "gas, grass, or ass"
bumper sticker over it.
포먼, 무슨 일이 있어도
우리가 네 옆에 있어줄게
Listen, Forman, whatever happens,
we'll all take the rap.
당연하지
Yeah.
차는 어쩌다 긁은 거냐, 에릭?
How'd you scratch the car, Eric?
- 잘 있어. 나중에 보자
- 또 보자, 포먼
- Have fun. Later.
- See you, Forman.
그래서?
Well?
그게요..
Well....
주차장에서 차를 빼고 있었어요
정말 살살 했는데...
Sir, I was pulling out of
this parking space.
Creeping is more like it.
I was creeping--
헛소리하지 마라
소화전에 박은 거잖아
You were screwing around,
backed into a hydrant.
- 페인트 자국보면 알아
- 아니에요!
- I see the paint marks.
- No!
아뇨, "정확하시다"고요
And by "no," I mean "exactly."
그치만 제 잘못이 아니었어요
켈소가 저한테 그걸 해서...
Yeah, but it wasn't my fault, sir.
Kelso was giving me a....
그거 뭐?
A what?
켈소가 저한테
젖꼭지 밤탱이를 했어요
Kelso was giving me
a purple nurple.
옷 위로 젖꼭지를 잡고
정말 세게 비트는 거에요
It's when you grab somebody's
nipple through their shirt...
and twist it really hard...
젖꼭지가 밤탱이 될 때까지요
until it becomes purple.
차 키 내놔라
Give me the keys.
아빠, 전...
Dad, I....
책임감이란 걸 배울 때까지
넌 운전금지다
Your driving privileges are suspended
until you learn some responsibility.
- 아빠, 저 책임감 있어요
- 아니, 없어
- Dad, I'm very responsible.
- No, you're not.
책임감있는 사람은 젖꼭지나
비틀리면서 다니지 않아
Responsible people don't go around
getting their nipples twisted.
보세요, 아빠가 말씀하셔도
정말 묘하게 들리잖아요
See, when you say it though,
it just sounds weird.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x14 Stolen Car
Jan 24, 1998 on FOX
에릭이 흠모하는 피겨 스케이팅 스타
도로시 하밀입니다
Love!
어머머
Oh, my God.
"멋진, 혹은 후진 헤어스타일의
올림픽 금메달리스트들"이래
"Hair Do's and Don'ts
of Olympic Gold Medalists."
세상에, 도로시 하밀이잖아?
이 여자 처녀야
Oh, my God, is that Dorothy Hamill?
She's a virgin.
있잖아...
Speaking of....
그거 해봤다는 애들 말야
할 때마다 좋았대?
You know, those girls at school
who do it, like, all the time?
그래
Yeah.
그냥 내 생각이 그런 거니, 아니면
걔들이 정말 더 여유있어 보이는 거니?
All right, is it just me,
or do they seem more relaxed?
안녕?
Hi.
너희들 뭐하고 있었어?
What are you guys doing?
섹스 얘기하고 있었을 거야
They are talking about sex.
왜 이래, 페즈
계집애들은 섹스 얘기 안해
Come on, Fez,
chicks don't talk about sex, man.
추잡하잖아
It's dirty.
우리도 해
Yes, we do.
특히 내 이상형 애인
마이클 켈소 얘기라면 더더욱
Especially when it involves Michael
Kelso, my dreamboat.
잘 났다. 인제 재키와 켈소의 성생활
얘기나 하고 있어야 겠네
Great. Now we have to talk about
Jackie and Kelso's sex life.
정말 인생 최악의 악몽일 거야
This is my worst nightmare.
너희들 들어오기 전에 재키랑 난
재밌는 시간을 보내고 있었어
All right, you know what?
Before you guys got here...
Jackie and I were actually
having a pretty good time.
나도 알아
나도 정말 놀랬다니까
I know. I was surprised, too.
도나, 우리집에 갈래?
Donna, you wanna go to my house?
좋아
You know what? Okay.
그래서 니들은 뭐하고 싶은데?
So what do you guys wanna do?
걸어서 허브에 가도 되고
We could walk to The Hub.
너무 멀어
Too far.
- 걸어서...
- 너무 멀어
- We could walk to--
- Too far.
정말 엿 같아
Man, this sucks.
쬐금 긁힌 거 갖고 차를 뺏어 버리다니
이건 정말 말도 안돼
I just can't believe
that Red took away my car...
because of one stupid little scratch.
맞아, 아저씨가 그렇게 오바하실 줄
누가 알았겠냐?
I know, man. Who would
think Red would overreact?
난 알았어
I did.
난 아저씨가 정말 꼬장꼬장한
인간이란 거 알고 있었거든
I have noticed Red is
a real hard-ass.
선밖으로 발가락 하나만 삐져나와도
바로 아주 아작을 내실거야
One toe over the line,
sweet Jesus, you are clobbered.
무슨 말인지 알지?
You know what I'm saying?
얘들아, 이것 좀 봐
Hey, guys. Check it out.
차 구했어?
Did you get a car?
그래, 사촌 셜리가 차를 빌려 줬어
Yeah. My cousin Sully
loaned me his wheels.
- 좋았어
- 그럼 어디 갈까?
- Yes.
- So where to?
그냥 여기서 개길래?
You just want to hang?
- 그래
- 좋아
- Yeah.
- Cool.
멍멍아?
Snookums?
왜, 애기야?
Yes, Pookie?
오늘 저녁 칠면조 샌드위치 먹을래
아니면 참치 샌드위치 먹을래?
Do you want turkey or tuna
sandwiches tonight for dinner?
오늘 저녁에?
Tonight?
Tonight's meatloaf night.
오늘은 미트로프 먹는 날이잖아
맞아요, 그치만 난 오늘밤 케노샤의
커뮤니티 대학에서 수업이 있어요
Right, but I have my class...
at the community college
in Kenosha tonight.
지난주에 말했잖아요
I told you about it last week.
그런 말 한 적 없는거 같은데
You most certainly did not.
했어요, 기억 안나요?
Yes, I did, remember?
당신 그때 '배레타' 보고 있었잖아요
터프가이 형사 드라마
You were watching Baretta.
여보, 내가 '배레타' 볼 때
나한테 말 시키면 안 되지
Midge, you can't tell me anything
while I'm watching Baretta.
헷갈리잖아
It's complicated.
여보, 내 정신세계를 넓히고 싶다고
몇 달전부터 말했잖아요
Bob, I've been telling you for months
how I've needed to expand my mind.
보석 얘기하는 거야?
보석이라면 사줄게
Is this about jewelry?
'Cause I'll buy you jewelry.
아니, 여보. 이건 내가 완전한 인간이
되는 거에 대한 얘기예요
No, sweetie. It's about me
becoming a whole person.
여보, 오해는 안 했으면 좋겠는데
그거 정말 바보짓이야
Midgie, don't take this the wrong way,
but that's just stupid.
당신이 결정할 문제가 아니에요
I don't think it's your decision.
이 집의 가장으로서 말하는데
커뮤니티 대학에 가지 마
I'm the man of the house...
and I say you're not going
to community college.
나한테 이래라 저래라 하지 마
이 곰탱아!
You can't tell me what to do,
you big ass!
뭘 보고 있는 거예요?
What are we looking at?
여기 긁힌 자국
That scratch.
어디요?
What scratch?
여기 에릭이
긁어 놓은 자국 말야
The scratch that Eric put in the car.
내가 흠집 제거제로
거의 없앴으니까 그렇지
I got most of it out
with rubbing compound...
원래 어땠는지
당신이 몰라서 그래
but you should have seen it before.
장난 아녔단 말야
It was a doozy.
굉장한 사고였겠네요
누가 죽었데요?
That must have been quite
an accident. Was he killed?
그 녀석 주둥이에서 나온 얘기도
바로 그거였어
See, that's where
his smart mouth comes from.
안전운전은 중요한 문제야, 여보
Driver safety is
serious business, Kitty.
당신이 옳아요
우리가 따끔하게 가르쳐야 겠어요
You're right, Red.
We should teach him a lesson.
걔가 집에 돌아오면 내가 잡고 있을테니
당신이 담배불로 지져버려요
So when he comes home,
I'll hold him down...
and you burn him with a cigarette.
있지, 도나
나 마이클이랑 하기로 마음먹고
Just so you know, Donna, when I
finally decide to do it with Michael...
모든 걸 다 계획해 뒀어
I have the whole thing planned out.
우선..
First...
난 아주 섹시한 "르노아르"를
입고 있을 거야
I'll be wearing a very sexy Renoir.
"페뇨아르(나이트 가운)" 아냐?
Don't you mean peignoir?
그래, 뭐가 됐든
분위기 깨지 좀 마, 도나
Yeah, okay, whatever.
Stop ruining this, Donna.
알았어
Okay.
그 다음엔 방에
온통 촛불을 켜두는 거야
And then
there'll be candles everywhere.
거기다, 또 아주 커다란
플래카드도 걸 거야
And also,
there'll be a gigantic banner.
그 다음 마이클이 들어오는 거지
And then Michael will come in.
그때 바람이 부는 거야
And the wind will be blowing...
그리고는 우리 인생에서
가장 환상적인 밤을 보내는 거지
and then we will have
the most magical night of our lives.
근데, 그렇게 계획까지
다 세워 놨으면서
So, if you have it all planned out...
왜 아직도 안 하고 있는 거야?
why are you still waiting?
난 그게 정말 특별했으면 좋겠거든
I want it to be really special.
커다란 플래카드까지 달고
어떻게 안 특별할 수 있겠니?
I mean, how could it not
with a gigantic banner?
바로 그거야
Exactly.
그이가 수업을 못듣게 해요
그치만 이거 너무 신날 것 같아요
Bob doesn't want me to take this
class, but it sounds so exciting.
전부 여권신장에 관한 거예요
It's all about female empowerment.
It's called, "The Woman Warrior:
"여전사: 여성고정관념과 싸우다"
"Fighting Female Stereotypes."
이 사람이 강사인데
귀엽지 않아요?
That's the professor.
Isn't he cute?
매력있네요
Darling.
그럼 같이 갈래요?
So you want to come?
끌리지 않는다고는 말 못하겠네요
I can't say I'm not tempted.
아뇨, 말할 수 있어요
별로 안 끌려요
Yes, I can. I'm not tempted.
힘있는 여성이 되고 싶지 않아요?
Don't you want to become
an empowered woman?
있죠, 난 그냥.. 힘있는 여성이
될 시간이 없어요
You know, I just.... I don't have time
to be an empowered woman.
살림만 하기도 너무 바쁘거든요
I'm too busy running this household.
자긴 운이 좋아요, 키티. 다 가졌잖아요
좋은 가족에 좋은 직업까지요
You're so lucky, Kitty. You have it all.
A great family and a great career.
레드를 어떻게 설득했길래
일을 할 수 있게 된 거예요?
How did you talk Red into
letting you work?
그게요, 어느날 둘이 앉아서
청구서를 정리하는데
Okay, well, one day we sat down,
we did all our bills...
우리가 집을 잃게 생겼다는 걸
깨달았지 뭐예요
and we realized we were
going to lose the house.
이 뒷좌석 엿같아
This backseat sucks.
게다가 너무 좁아
페즈 다리가 내 다리를 건드리고 있어
Plus it's too small.
Fez's leg is touching mine.
아냐. 니 꺼가 내 껄
건드리는 거야
No. Your leg is touching mine.
뒷좌석엔 탈 일도 없었는데
I shouldn't even be
in the back seat.
난 내 차를 몰았어야 된단 말야
You know, I should be
driving my own car.
네가 네 차를 못 몰고 있는
이유는 말야, 포먼
The reason you're not
driving your own car, Forman...
네가 책임감없이
차를 긁었기 때문이잖아
is because you're irresponsible,
and you scratched it.
맞았어, 바로 그거야
Yeah. That's a good one.
나 운전하고 있잖아!
I'm trying to drive the car here, man!
아까 거기 나둬
나 그 노래 좋아해
No. Put it back, I like that song.
뒷좌석 맹구는 조용히 하셔
Pipe down, now, back seat Charlie.
'Deep Purple'의 "Highway Star"
좋았어
All right.
뒷 좌석 엿같아
The back seat sucks.
나의 작고 슬픈 세계에
온 걸 환영해
Welcome to my sad little world.
오늘 저녁 퇴근 운전길에도
When you
drive home tonight...
안전운전 잊지 마십시오
please remember to drive carefully.
젠장, 피클이 없어
다시 돌아가야겠다
Great, no pickles.
Now we gotta go back.
닥쳐!
Shut up!
근데 셜리는 왜 대쉬보드에
마리아상을 붙여 놓은 거야?
Why does Sully have a statue
of the Virgin Mary on his dashboard?
신자인가 보지 뭐
Maybe he's, like,
religious or something.
그 사람 방화죄로
감방간적 있지 않아?
Wasn't Sully in prison for arson?
맞아
Yeah.
불지르고 다니는 사람들도
하느님은 믿는단다, 하이드
People who burn stuff
believe in God, too, Hyde.
열쇠고리에 있는
"난 빙고를 사랑해" 는 또 뭐야?
Why does his key chain say,
"I love Bingo"?
셜리가 빙고를 사랑하나 보지
Sully must love Bingo.
난 이 차가 셜리 차가 아닐지도
모른다는 생각이 들기 시작했어
All right, I'm starting to think
that maybe this isn't Sully's car.
그럼 누구 찬데?
Then whose car is it?
난리 났군. 난 이제 죽었다
This is great. I'm dead.
다들 내 차 타고
내가 하자는 대로 할 때는
When we were in my car,
and I was running the show...
이렇게 다같이 감방 들어온 적
한번도 없었어
I don't remember
one single time we all got arrested.
맞아
That's true.
에릭, 좀 진정할래?
여기 너만 큰일난 게 아냐
Eric, will you just relax?
We're all in trouble here.
아니, 아니지, 아냐
No.
다 같이 큰일난 게 아니지
We're not all in trouble here.
너희 부모님은 애가 일곱이라서
Your parents have seven kids.
너는 없어진 줄도 모르실 거야
They won't even notice
you're gone.
너희 부모님은
이 나라에 살지도 않으시고
Your parents don't even
live in this country.
그리고 너희 엄마는
And your mom,
probably one cell over.
아마 여기 옆방에 계실 걸?
그러니까, 나는 너희와 달라
So, that just leaves me.
여기서 큰일난 사람은
나 뿐이야
I'm the only one
who's really in trouble here.
우리 엄마 술 깨자 마자
나도 너처럼 큰일나는 거야
Look, Forman, I'll be
in as much trouble as you as are...
as soon as Edna sobers up.
난 추방당할 거야
I will be deported.
난 내 고향으로 돌려 보내지게 될 거야
아름다운 섬인....
They're gonna send me back
to my homeland, the beautiful island of--
좋아, 여기 주모자가 누구냐?
Okay, who's the ringleader here?
얘요!
He is.
- 전화는 한 통화만이다
- 어디든 해도 돼요?
- You get one phone call.
- To anywhere?
시내전화 한 통화다
One local phone call.
그래서 누가 전화할 거야?
So who should we call?
아빠한테 전화하느니
안전한 감옥에 있을래
I'd call Red, but I feel safer in jail.
나 전화번호 몰라요
I don't know my phone number.
우리 엄마한테는 하나 마나야
포커치러 가는 날이거든
I can't call Edna, man.
It's poker night.
미안한 얘기지만, 니 엄마는
매일 저녁 포커치시지 않냐?
No offense, but isn't every night
poker night for Edna?
그래, 알았다
내가 재키한테 걸게
I know. I got it.
I'll call Jackie.
걔네 아빠가 변호사잖아
Her dad's a lawyer,
and she's got a checkbook.
게다가 걘 수표책도 있어
여보세요?
Hello?
재키! 다행히 집에 있었구나
Jackie! Thank God you're home.
나 훔친 차를 몰다가 체포됐어
I was driving a stolen car
and I got arrested.
마이클, 소설 "사랑의 죄수" 같다
Michael, this is
just like the book Prisoner of Love...
터프하지만 사랑스런 오토바이 정비공
클리프가 감옥에 갇히자
where Cliff, the rugged yet sweet
motorcycle mechanic was thrown into jail.
그의 연인 타샤는 비열한 부자의
노예가 될 것을 강요당해
And then his true love, Tasha,
was forced to be a slave girl...
for this really rich, mean guy.
재키, 나 농담하는 거 아냐
나 진짜 감옥에 있어
Jackie, I'm not kidding around.
I'm really in jail.
세상에, 괜찮니?
My God. Are you okay?
그런 거 같아
그치만 약간 추워
Yeah, I guess.
But I'm a little cold.
감방은 너무 외로워, 재키
It's lonely in the joint, Jackie.
세상에, 너 진짜 감옥에 있구나
My God. You're really in jail.
영영 못 나오면 어떡하지?
What if you never get out?
그럼 정말 인생 꼬이는 거지
That would really suck.
그래, 마이클. 네가 감옥에서 나오면
내 사랑을 증명해 줄께, 약속해
Yes, it would, Michael.
And I promise...
the minute you get out of prison,
I'm gonna prove my love to you.
멋진데, 고마워
Cool. Thanks.
마이클, 내 말 무슨 뜻인지
알기는 하는 거니?
Michael, do you even know
what I'm saying to you?
응
Yeah.
아니
No.
섹스해 주겠단 말야, 이 바보야
We're gonna make love, you idiot.
좋았어!
All right!
둘이서 즐거운 담소라도 나눴냐?
You two have a nice little talk?
오~예
Yeah.
- 재밌는 게 뭔지 알아?
- 뭔데?
- You know what's funny?
- What?
없어! 이 바보야. 너 걔한테
도와달라는 말은 하지도 않았잖아
Nothing! Because you forgot
to ask her for help, you moron!
아, 맞다
My God, you're right.
동전 하나 더 줘봐
Give me another dime.
동전 하나밖에 없었어
We only had one dime.
한통화 밖에
못하는 거였단 말야
We only got one phone call.
이런
My God.
누가 숟가락 하나만 줘봐
내가 땅굴 팔테니까 탈출하자
Somebody give me a spoon.
I'm gonna dig my way out of here.
이 녀석 좀 봐
저녁 먹을 때가 다 됐는데
Look at this.
Here we are sitting down to dinner...
이 녀석은 아직 집에도 안 왔어
and Eric's not even home yet.
여보, 당신이 차를 뺏었잖아요
걘 이제 걸어다녀야 된단 말이에요
Honey, you took away his car.
He has to walk everywhere.
걷는 게 건강에 좋아
Walking is good for him.
여보, 걔한테 왜 그렇게
엄하게 대해요?
Red, why do you have to be
so hard on him?
우리 노친네가 나한테
엄하게 한 거랑 같은 이유지
Same reason my old man
was hard on me.
세상에 나갈 준비를 시키는 것
To prepare me for the world.
여보, 내가 그 녀석 나이 땐
You know, Kitty,
when I was his age...
아무 것도 없이
맥가이버 칼 하나 가지고
I could have parachuted
onto a deserted island...
낙하산 타고 무인도에 떨어져도
난 살아남았을 거야
with nothing but a Swiss army knife,
and I would've survived.
그래도 교훈은 있는 얘기네요
에릭한테 스카이다이빙은 안 된다
Okay, then we've learned something.
No skydiving for Eric.
내 말 좀 들어봐, 여보
세상은 험난한 곳이야
I'll tell you, Kitty,
the world is a tough place.
눈만 깜빡해도
You drop your guard
for one second...
코 베어가는 세상이란 말야
and it'll kick you right in the ass.
당신이 옳아요
Well, you're right.
세상은 험난하죠
Red, the world is hard.
그러니까 걔가 집에서 만이라도
편안하면 좋지 않겠어요?
So wouldn't it be nice if Eric came
home to a place that wasn't?
알았어, 여보
이담에 복권 당첨되거든
All right, Kitty,
when you win the lottery...
그 녀석한테
디즈니랜드를 사 주구려
you can buy him Disneyland.
정말 수업 들으러
가버리다니
I can't believe
she went to that class.
결혼한 여자가
자기 가정을 내버리면 안 되지
Married women do not
abandon their families.
괜찮아요, 아빠
70년대잖아요
Sure they do, Dad.
It's the '70s.
세상이 바뀐 건 나도 알아
I know what decade it is.
그래도 따뜻한 음식 대신
샌드위치를 먹고있단 사실은 바뀌지 않아
Doesn't change the fact I'm eating
a sandwich instead of a hot meal.
전자렌지에 돌려 드릴까요?
You want me to
microwave it for you?
난 네 엄마가
왜 이러는지 모르겠구나
I just don't understand
why she needs this.
내가 잘 살게 해줬잖아
I've given her a great life.
아빠, 그게 중요한 게 아니에요
Dad, that's not the issue.
남녀 평등 헌법 수정안의 핵심은
The whole point of the
Equal Rights Amendment...
여성이 남성에 의해 좌우되는
존재가 아니라는 거예요
is so that women don't have to
define themselves by a man.
도나, 옷 얘기하는 거냐?
옷이라면 사주마
Donna, is this about clothes?
'Cause I can buy you clothes.
입만 아프네요
This is pointless.
아빠 맥주 갖다주러 가는 거지?
While you're up,
you wanna get daddy a beer?
아가?
Honey?
에릭, 니가 어떻게 좀 해봐
Eric, you've gotta do
something, man.
내가? 넌 왜 안되는데, 켈소?
아니면 하이드는?
Me? What about you, Kelso?
Or Hyde?
난 경찰이랑 말 못해
열받아서 돌아버릴 거거든
I can't talk to cops, man.
I go insane with rage.
나도 그래, 경찰은 똘아이들이야
And me, too. Nuts.
에릭, 우리 좀 살려줘
Eric, you gotta help us.
그래서 나더러 다시
총대를 매라고?
So now I'm back in charge?
맨날 이 모양이지
This is so typical.
좋아, 알았다고
Okay, you know what? Fine.
다시 한번 내가 남자답게 나서서
염치없는 네 놈들을 구해주지
Once again, I'll suck it up, be the
man and save all your sorry asses.
경관님, 드릴 말씀이 있어요
Officer, I need to talk to you, please.
저 좀 내보내 주세요!
You gotta let me go!
제발요, 우리 아빠가
절 죽일 거예요
Please, God.
My dad's gonna kill me.
넌 차를 훔쳤어, 꼬마야
You stole a car, kid.
그런 널 풀어주면 난 뭐가 되겠냐?
What kind of cop would I be
if I just let you go?
제 가장 좋은 친구 경찰요?
My best friend the cop?
정말 제 잘못이 아니에요
친구한테서 빌린 차예요
Look, it really wasn't my fault.
We borrowed it from a friend.
그래, 그런 얘기 처음 들었을 거 같냐?
어이, 이거 좀 들어봐
Yeah, haven't heard that one before.
Guess what?
이 녀석들 차를 훔친 게 아니라
친구한테서 빌린 거래
They didn't really steal the car.
They borrowed it from a friend.
사실이야
Actually, they did.
셜리라는 친구가 자기 할머니한테서
그 차를 빌렸었는데
Turns out this guy Sully
borrowed it from his grandmother...
할머니가 깜빡하고
도난신고를 했대
and she forgot
and called it in stolen.
그래도 괞찮은 노인네더라고
빙고 게임을 한대
Nice old lady, though.
She plays Bingo.
잘 됐네요
그럼 우리 가도 되죠?
My God, this is great.
So, we're free to go?
그래. 이름이 뭐냐?
Yeah. Which one are you?
에릭 포먼이요
Eric Forman.
포먼?
너희 아빠가 레드 포먼이냐?
Forman?
Is your dad Red Forman?
네
Yeah.
이 불쌍한 자식
You poor bastard.
- 고맙습니다
- 여깄다
- Well, thank you.
- Here.
어떻게 됐어?
So?
택시 불러
석방이야
So call a cab.
We're sprung.
뭐? 풀려나는 거야?
What? We're free?
모든 혐의가 풀렸어
All charges dropped.
이게 너희들이 원했던 거지?
Wait, that is what you wanted, right?
- 당장 여기서 나가자
- 그래
- Let's get the hell out of here.
- Yeah.
나 왔어요
Hi, Bob.
여보, 생각해 봤는데
Midge, I've been thinking.
당신이 그 수업을 들어서 행복하다면
나도 행복할 거 같아
If taking that class made you happy,
then I guess I'm happy.
나한테 얼마나 소중하다구요
일주일에 딱 두번이에요, 그러니...
Sweetie, it means so much to me.
And it's only twice a week, so it's not--
잠깐, 잠깐
Whoa.
난 이번 한번인줄 알았는데
I thought this was a one-time deal.
여보, 여권신장이란 건
하루 만에 다 배울 수 없어요
Bob, you can't learn total
female empowerment in one night.
10일은 걸린다구요
It takes 10 nights.
잠깐만, 여보
Wait. Midge,
다시는 가지 마
you are not going back.
전쟁의 여신, 아프로디테는
그걸 받아들이지 않을 거고
Aphrodite, the Goddess of War
wouldn't take this...
나도 마찬가지예요!
and neither will I!
- 저 왔어요
- 잠깐
- Hey, Dad.
- Hold it.
차 말인데
About the car.
나도 안다, 그게..
I know it was....
그래서 난...
And I....
나 어릴 땐 있잖냐...
You see, when I was a kid....
어쩌면 내가 좀...
Maybe I came down....
차 키나 받아라
Here's the keys.
감사합니다
Thank you, sir.
- 그런데 저녁내 어디 있었던 거냐?
- 감방에요
- So where you been all night?
- Prison.
그래, 잘했다
Yeah, okay.
재키
Jackie.
마이클, 너 출옥했구나
Michael, you've been sprung.
그 안이 어땠는지
넌 모를 거야, 재키
You don't know what it's like
on the inside, Jackie.
너 맞았니?
Did they beat you?
응
Yeah.
이 망할 짭새들
Damn those police.
아냐, 하이드가 때렸어
그치만 개구리잡듯 팼단 말야
No. It was Hyde.
But he really frogged me.
불쌍한 내 새끼
Poor baby.
고마워, 재키
Thanks, Jackie.
- 좋아, 그거 얼른 하자
- 너무 완벽해
- Okay, so let's do this thing.
- This is so perfect.
난 야한 잠옷이나 해적 셔츠나
바람같은 건 바라지도 않아
I don't even miss the peignoir,
the pirate shirt, or the wind.
플래카드는?
What about the banner?
괜찮아
It's okay.
중요한 건 우리가
여기 함께 있다는 거야
The important thing is,
I'm here with you.
난 너한테 나를 줄 준비가 됐어
And I'm prepared to
give myself to you...
몸과 마음과 영혼까지도
body, mind, and soul.
마이클, 이 밤은 우리 인생에서
가장 환상적인 밤이 될 거야
Michael, this is going to be
the most magical night of our lives.
맞다, 한가지 더
Yeah, and one more thing.
우리 부모님 슈퍼마켓 가셨으니까
시간이 15분 정도 밖에 없어
My parents are at the A&P,
so we only have, like, 15 minutes.
다들 햄버거 맛 괜찮냐?
You guys enjoying your burgers?
피클도 많이 들어 있지?
팻소 버거에서는 많이 넣어 주거든
Got enough pickles on them?
That's how Fatso Burger does them.
무진장 많은 피클
그럼, 그럼
Lots and lots of pickles. Yes, yes.
그래. 정말 좋다
Yeah. It's great.
거기 뒷자리 좁지 않지?
Got enough room back there?
사실은, 많이 타서 좀 좁아
Actually, it's a little bit crowded.
좋아. 그래야지
Good. That's the way
it should be. Yes, yes.
그럼, 그럼
난 영화보러 가고 싶은데
니들은 가고 싶은 데 있냐?
I feel like going to the movies.
Where do you guys wanna go?
- 저수지 가자
- 영화보러 갈거야
- Let's go to the reservoir.
- Movies it is. Yes, yes.
그럼, 그럼
난 저수지 가고 싶은데
I kind of feel like going to
the reservoir.
저수지 갈 거야
Reservoir it is. Yes, yes.
그럼, 그럼
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24